wendys.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Wendy's

Welcome! Thank you for visiting an offering owned and operated by Wendy’s International, LLC. To help inform you, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of information you submit or we collect through our website www.wendys.com and our other related mobile websites, mobile Wendy’s applications (“mobile apps”), services, tools, and other applications (collectively, the “Site”). A reference to “Wendy’s,” “our,” “we,” or “us” includes Wendy’s International, LLC and each of its related, affiliated, parent or subsidiary companies.

**Contents & Summary**

A table summarizing the contents of this privacy policy and notice (this “Privacy Policy”) appears below, followed by the Privacy Policy in full. Should there be any discrepancy between the table and the full Privacy Policy, the language of the full Privacy Policy shall govern.

| 

By using the Site you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information and other information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site is also governed by the [Terms of Use](https://www.wendys.com/terms-and-conditions), [Mobile Apps Policy](https://www.wendys.com/mobile-apps-policy),  [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank) and [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking).  
  
---|---  

| 

We collect the following information when you use the Site:  
  
| 

 (a) [Registration and Account Information:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22reginfo)

| 

When you create an account or profile on the Site, you voluntarily give us personal information  
  
| 

 (b) [MyWendy’s™ Account Information:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22MyWendys)

| 

When you create a MyWendy’s account, you voluntarily give us personal information.  
  
| 

 (c) [Career Registrations:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22careerreg)

| 

When you register to receive job alerts or apply for a job, you voluntarily give us personal and non-personal information. For more information, see our  [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank).  
  
| 

 (d) [Information to Respond to Your Requests:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22respond2req)

| 

You may also give us your personal information to sign up for our newsletters and other communications.  
  
| 

 (e) [Social Media Information:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22socialmediainfo)

| 

If you sign in to your MyWendy’s account through third-party social media sites like Facebook or Twitter, you agree to give us ongoing access to some of your personal information.  
  
| 

(f) [Information From Other Sources:](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22infoother)

| 

We may, on occasion, combine information from outside sources to customize your experience on the Site.  
  
| 

(g) [Information You Post on the Site](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22infopost):

| 

You may provide us with information regarding your personal beliefs, opinions, and background by completing a profile, or by posting recommendations, comments, or ratings on the Site.  
  
| 

(h) [Mobile Information](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22mobileinfo):

| 

We may collect additional information from you if you access our Site through a mobile device (e.g., your unique device identifier, your device’s operating system, or the mobile carrier for your phone).  
  
| 

(i) [Technical Usage Information](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22techusage):

| 

We use tracking technologies such as cookies and other similar technologies to measure usage. For more information about the use of cookies and similar technologies on our Site, please review our [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy.](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking)  
  
| 

(j) [Location/Geolocation](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22geolocal):

| 

By using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection and use of your location and/or geolocation information.  

| 

We use information collected from you to operate the Site and contact you. Your information is retained for as long as we need it for our business.  

| 

We may share your personal information and other information we collect with the following entities: (a) Wendy’s; (b) our service providers and other third parties; (c) other entities with your consent; (d) legal and law enforcement; (e) other entities in the event of a change of control; and (f) companies in the mobile app industry if you access the Site via a mobile device or app.  

| 

You can control how and when you want to receive notifications from Wendy’s on the Site or by following instructions within the notifications.  

| 

We use tracking technologies (including cookies) to recognize you, protect your privacy, customize your experience on the Site, and target the content/advertising you see, including providing videos customized to your interests. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or third-party social media.  

| 

You can review and edit your personal information by accessing your account on the Site.  

| 

If you are a California resident, you may request information about our practices related to disclosing your personal information and how we respond to Do Not Track signals.  

| 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party websites that are linked to or from the Site.  

| 

We protect your personal information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration.  

| 

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13.  

| 

We store and process your personal information on our computer systems in the U.S. and elsewhere in the world.  

| 

You agree that we may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting notices on the Site.  

| 

For more information about our privacy practices, go to our full [Privacy Policy](https://www.wendys.com/privacy-policy) or send an email to [privacy@Wendys.com](mailto:privacy@Wendys.com).  
  
**Privacy Policy**

**1\. Scope and Consent**

When you use the Site, you are contracting with Wendy’s located at One Dave Thomas Blvd., Dublin, OH 43017, USA. If you reside outside of the United States, Wendy’s is your data controller. By using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, the [Terms of Use](https://www.wendys.com/terms-and-conditions), [Mobile Apps Policy](https://www.wendys.com/mobile-apps-policy), [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/) and [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking).

**2\. Information We Collect**

When you use the Site, we or third party service providers acting on our behalf may collect the following information:

**        a. Registration and Account Information:**

You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or providing any personal information (e.g., name, email address, telephone phone number, mobile telephone number, payment information or contact information) about yourself. When you register an account, create a profile, purchase products, or otherwise engage with the Site, you may provide personal information. Personal information is only associated with your account/profile when you sign in as a registered user.

         **b. By Wendy’s  Account Registration:  **

If you register for a MyWendy’s account, you choose to give us your personal information and are not anonymous to us. In addition to personal information, you may also provide us with non-personal information (e.g., your opinions regarding products or menu/program/services preferences). You may also provide us with your credit or debit card information and/or gift card numbers if you are making a purchase.

         **c. Career Registrations:**

The Careers section of the Site gives you the opportunity to create a “General Account” to receive job alerts and an “Application Account” to apply for jobs.

  * General Account: To register for a General Account, you will provide us with certain personal information and non-personal information (e.g., education level, job preferences, job level, schedule, availability to travel, job type and geographic area).
  * Application Account:  To apply for a position, you will need to establish an “Application Account.” In order to do so, you will provide us with your email address, password and secret question that will allow you to access your account later. Also, when you apply for a job or authorize us to obtain a consumer report (e.g., background check), we will collect personal and non-personal information (e.g., name, address, telephone number, resume, employment history, reference information, compensation, education and compensation history, and social security number or social insurance number). Also, you may upload your photo to the website on your resume.

Visit our [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank) for more information regarding the types of career information we collect and how we treat that information.

**        d. Information to Respond to Your Requests: **

You may give us your personal information so we can send you newsletters and other communications you request. Details of how you can opt-out of receiving any communications from us are detailed in [Section 5](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22yourchoices) of this Privacy Policy.

**        e. Social Media Information: **

We also may offer services that allow you to share information with third party social media websites such as Facebook, Pinterest, Google Plus, Twitter, and others. We may also offer social networking sign-on services that allow you to use social networking credentials to access the Site. We may collect information about you in connection with social networking sites when you use these sign-on features.

When you engage with our Site through third party social media sites, you understand that you may be allowing us to have ongoing access to certain information stored on those social media sites (e.g., your public profile, friend list, people you follow or who follow you, your email address, birthday, work history, education history, interests, current city, website, personal description and likes, and your friends’ birthdays, education histories, personal descriptions and likes). We may also receive other information (e.g., content viewed and information about the advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with the Site. You agree that we may share your video viewing with or obtain information about your video viewing from third party social media sites for up to two years (or as permitted by applicable law) or until you withdraw consent. The information we have access to from the third party social media websites varies by website and is controlled by your privacy settings on that website and by your consent. By associating an account managed by a third party with your MyWendy’s account or otherwise engaging with the Site through a social network and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, use, and store information from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**         f. Information from Other Sources: **

The information we collect may be combined with information from outside records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, additional contact information, and for job applicants, with your consent, a credit report) that we have acquired in accordance with applicable law.

**       g. Content You Post and Associate with Your Profile on the Site:**

Certain sections of the Site give you an opportunity to provide us with information regarding your opinions and reviews of products and services. In addition, the content you post and recommendations you make may provide information about your beliefs to us.

**        h. Mobile Information: **

We or third parties may collect additional information from you if you access the Site through a mobile device (e.g., your unique device identifier, unique device token to facilitate push notifications through mobile apps, your device’s advertising identifier, your device’s operating system, identifiers associated with equipment or systems used in connection with your device (e.g., an identifier of a Wi-Fi router or Internet access point), mobile manufacturer or carrier, mobile or data network systems or operators, other providers of other apps or code on your device, anyone who has administrative privileges to devices you use, location or GPS/geolocation, mobile number, your email address, user name, passwords, and financial or payment information). You agree to our collection of this data (including location and/or geolocation data) and the sharing and disclosing of this data with the third parties and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy (e.g., web analytics companies, Wendy's independently-operated franchisees (“Franchisees”), social media networks or other third parties operating on our behalf). For more information about our information collection and use practices with respect to online services that are mobile applications (“Mobile Apps”) see the [Mobile Apps Policy](https://www.wendys.com/mobile-apps-policy) and any applicable Just in Time Notice in our Mobile Apps.

**        i. Technical Usage Information:**

When you visit the Site, we collect usage information sent to us by your computer, mobile device, or other access device that tells us how you are using the Site (“usage information”). We may use session unification and tracking technologies (including unique identifiers, unique device tokens, HTML5, cookies, flash cookies, web beacons/GIFs, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browsers) to collect usage information. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and/or connection information. During some visits we may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information.

Our goal is to collect and use only that information that we think is required for our legitimate business interests, in order to better understand your interests and improve your experience of using the Site. To learn more about how we use tracking technologies and cookies, see [Section 6](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22techtracking) of this Privacy Policy and our [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy.](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking)

**        j. Location / Geolocation Information:  **

When you visit the Site, we may collect location and/or geolocation information to provide certain location-based services that you request (e.g., maps) or for any of the reasons set forth in [Section 3](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22uses) of this Privacy Policy. We may share and disclose the location and/or geolocation data in the manner set forth in [Section 4](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22disclosure) of this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Uses and Retention**

Information collected on the Site may be used for the following purposes:

**        a. Operate Our Site: **We use the information collected to: (i) respond to your requests; (ii) provide customer service (e.g., to resolve disputes or problems with your account/profile or the Site); (iii) personalize your experience by providing content on the Site, including targeted advertising, that we believe may be of most interest to you; (iv) improve the Site; (v) give you information about your account; (vi) manage Site traffic; (vii) assess promotional effectiveness; (viii) administer surveys, clubs, promotions (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, reward and loyalty programs); (ix) manage your purchases (e.g., remember shopping cart information); (x) marketing purposes; (xi) to improve products and services; (xii) consider your job application; and (xiii) provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience.

        **b. Analyze and Aggregate Non-Personal Information:**  We use aggregate information about our users and non-personal information to analyze Site and user behavior, including, for example, browser information and referring website address. We may also use this information to prepare aggregated reports (e.g., total number of visitors, IP addresses, browser types, access times, pages viewed and referring website addresses).

        **c. Prevent Fraud:  **We use information from the Site, collected by us or third party service providers that work on our behalf, to prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, security breaches, and potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our [Terms of Use](https://www.wendys.com/terms-and-conditions). This may include, in our sole discretion, limiting the number of accounts per individual or household, terminating accounts, prosecuting abuse to the fullest extent of the law, or other measures.

**       d. Communication Wih You: **We use your information to contact you to maintain the Site, your account, or to comply with your stated communication preferences (e.g., for newsletters), or to provide other services requested by you, as described at the time when we collect the information from you, or to contact you for other purposes authorized by law.

**        e. Mobile Data: **When you access the Site on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy. For example, by virtue of your use of the Site, you expressly consent to our use of location information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, coupons, search results, and other personalized content.

**        f. Analytics: **We use third party service providers to help us provide certain features on the Site and analyze our visitors' preferences, such as Google Analytics. These partners may use cookies and similar technologies described above to collect and analyze information about use of our websites and mobile applications. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices at _http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/_ , and opt out by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on, available at  _https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout_.

**        g. Device Data: ** If you use different devices (such as your home computer, laptop, mobile device and/or other smart device) to access the Site, we may be able to associate you with each of your devices. For example, the Site may recognize your MyWendy’s account across devices. Information we have collected from your different devices may be combined with other information you have provided us, including information that is saved in your MyWendy’s account, your order history, how you use the Site, and the products you view. We may use this information to help provide more tailored experiences and consistent services across all of your devices as explained in this Privacy Policy. We may also use this information to prevent fraud, such as by identifying when your account is accessed from an unfamiliar device, or to provide customized offers or advertising based on your use of each device and your interactions with the Site. To opt-out or cancel this device tracking, you may cancel or delete your MyWendy’s account information. For more information on how you can exercise choices regarding cookie based tracking, see [Section 6](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22techtracking) of this Privacy Policy and our [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy.](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/cookies-and-tracking)

**        h. Your Career Interests: **Pursuant to our [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank), we may use information you provide to process your interest or application in a Wendy’s job position. See the [Career Submission Terms](https://careers.wendys.com/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank) for details.

You expressly consent to our lawful worldwide use of your personal information and that we may retain information as long as it is necessary and relevant for our business operations, including to effectuate your requests. Further, you consent to the ability of third party service providers working on our behalf to collect and retain personal information and non-personal usage information for Site operation purposes (e.g., fraud prevention). Further, you consent to our retention of your video viewing tracking data for up to two years (or as permitted by applicable law) or until you withdraw consent.

**1\. Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

Information collected on the Site may be shared or disclosed with the following parties:

**       a. Wendy's: **

We may share the information we collect about you within Wendy’s, and may disclose the information to Franchisees and third party service providers. The information may be shared or disclosed to: (i) provide joint content and our services (e.g., registration, transactions, analytics and customer support); (ii) help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud, and/or data security breaches; and (iii) guide decisions about Wendy’s or third party products, sites, applications, services, tools, and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications and you will have the opportunity to opt-out of our communications.

**        b. Service Providers and Other Third Parties:**

We may share or disclose your information to service providers who help with our business operations (such as, but not limited to, fraud investigations, bill collection, payment processing, gift card support, site analytics and operations). We may also facilitate our Site to permit third party service providers to collect information from you for security and fraud prevention purposes. On the Site, we may work with third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and site analytics and assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own tracking technologies/cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They might also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit and other information about you or your device in order to analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Site and elsewhere. For more information about third party ad servers at our Site and your ability to opt-out of targeted advertising from such third parties, please see [Section 6](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22techtracking) of this Privacy Policy and visit our [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking). If you have any questions about how our service providers manage your personal information, please contact us at the email address included in [Section 15](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22contact) of this Privacy Policy.

**        c. Other Entities with Your Consent:**

 We may share or disclose your information to other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). This may include, without limitation, third party social media networks such as Facebook, Pinterest, Google Plus, Twitter, and others. On the Site, you may have opportunities to express interest in or register for other services. If you do, we will provide information about you to those third parties, or parties working on their behalf, to implement your request.

**        d. Legal and Law Enforcement: **

We may share or disclose the information we collect about you as required or permitted by law, law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third parties, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other Wendy’s user to legal liability. In such events, we will only disclose information relevant and necessary to the investigation or inquiry, such as name, city, state/province/territory, ZIP/postal code, telephone number, email address, user ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and anything else we may deem relevant to the investigation.

**        e. Change of Control - New Owners:**

We may share or disclose your information to other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will make reasonable efforts to request that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information would be used contrary to this Privacy Policy, we will request that you receive prior notice.

**        f. Companies in the Mobile App Industry:**

If you access the Site through a mobile device or app, we may also share or disclose your information with companies in the mobile app industry, such as carriers, operating systems, and platforms, to provide or improve our products and services or for other purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  We will not share your personal information with companies in the mobile app industry for their marketing purposes without your consent.  

**2\. Your Choices**

You can control how and when you want to receive notifications from Wendy’s on the Site or by following instructions within the notices.

         **a.  Information You Share on the Site:**   If you post information or content, such as by participating in online forums or communities, or when you interact with our Site through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending upon your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. We cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. Please refer to those third party sites’ privacy policies and terms of use to learn more about their privacy practices, which we do not control.

         **b. Communication Preferences and Marketing (Opt-out):  **We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Site. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can indicate your communications preference within the direct communication from us or through your account/profile settings. You may not opt-out of administrative emails (e.g., emails about your transactions or policy changes) for your registered account.

**3\. Tracking Technologies (Cookies)  **

When you visit the Site, we and our business partners may use tracking technologies to enhance your online experience or customize our offerings.  Here are a few additional important things you should know about our use of tracking technologies (cookies):

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of tracking technologies.

  * We use both session and persistent tracking technologies. Tracking technologies (e.g. cookies) can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). You are always free to decline tracking technologies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site. Refer to the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling tracking technologies such as cookies.

  * We encode and protect the tracking technologies that Wendy’s sets, so that only Wendy’s and our designated service providers (e.g., our advertising and technology partners) can interpret the information stored in them.

  * You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third party service providers that we have allowed on our site that assist us with various aspects of our web site operations and services, such as Google Analytics, as further described above.

  * You also may encounter tracking technologies from third parties on certain pages of the websites that we do not control and have not authorized (e.g., if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page).

  * We may target and track the videos you view on the Site. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or third party social media for up to two years (or as permitted by applicable law) or until you withdraw consent

For more information about the use of cookies and similar technology on our online services, please review this Privacy Policy and our [Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy](https://www.wendys.com/cookies-and-tracking). For information about opt out programs that third party advertising companies participate in, and to opt out of the use of website browsing data for interest-based advertising by companies that participate in these programs, click the following: [NAI Opt Out](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1%22%20%5Cl%20%22!/%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank) and [DAA Opt Out](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank). To opt out of the use of data collected from the mobile applications on your mobile device to serve ads that are targeted to your interests, consult the settings on your device.

**4.  Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information**

Registered users can review and change their personal information at any time by accessing their accounts on the Site. You should promptly update your personal information if it changes or becomes inaccurate. We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our [Terms of Use](https://www.wendys.com/terms-and-conditions%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank), or take other actions permitted by law. We may also retain certain transaction history and other non-personal information to analyze user behavior. Likewise, if your account or membership is terminated or suspended, we may maintain some information to prevent re-registration. Unfortunately, if you close your account, we cannot reactivate it, but you are always welcome to open a new one.

**5.  Notice to California Residents**

  * Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which our online service has disclosed certain personal information (as defined by California law) during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us at: Wendy’s International, LLC, One Dave Thomas Boulevard, Dublin, OH 43017, USA, Attn: Chief Legal Officer, Legal Department. For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.
  * **How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals for California Residents:**  California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how Wendy’s responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. Wendy’s does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

**6.  Notice to Canadian Residents**

Residents of Canada may request access to the personal information in our custody and control. If you are a Canadian resident and would like to request access, please contact us at: Wendy’s International, LLC, One Dave Thomas Boulevard, Dublin, OH 43017, USA, Attn: Chief Legal Officer, Legal Department. For all requests, you must put the statement “Your Canadian Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name and sufficient information for us to identify you based on your interactions with Wendy’s. We may request additional personal information for the purposes of verifying your identity before we can respond to the request.

**7.  Third Parties**

Our Site may contain links to other third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party sites.

**8.  Security**

We store and process your information on our servers located within the United States. As we operate internationally, we may store and process your information on servers that are located outside of the United States.  We protect your personal information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use include data encryption, firewalls, regular security assessments of IT infrastructure, and access controls to physical, network-based and data assets. While we implement the above security measures on the Site, you should be aware that one hundred percent security is not always possible and, as a result, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. It is your responsibility to make sure that your personal information is accurate and that your passwords and account registration information is secure and not shared with third parties.

**9.  Children's Privacy**

The Site is a general audience site and it is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information via our websites, applications, services, or tools from users in this age group. If you believe your child has provided personal information to us, please contact us via the email listed in [Section 15](https://www.wendys.com/en-ca/privacy-policy%22%20%5Cl%20%22contact) below.

**10.  International Transfer**

The majority of our computer systems, networks, and devices are currently based in the United States. As we operate internationally, your personal information may be processed in the U.S. and elsewhere where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an account/profile, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personal information and tracking technologies/cookies as described in this Privacy Policy.

**11.  Notification Regarding Updates**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Site. You should check the Site frequently for updates. If Wendy’s or any third party to whom we disclose your personal information is required to provide notice of a security breach, you consent to receiving notice through this Site or via the email address you have provided to us, at our discretion.

**12.  Contact Us**

If your questions are not answered online, you may email us at privacy@wendys.com.

Last Updated: November [__], 2018
